Finding Aid for Student Advocacy Center of Michigan records, 1975-2004
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Digital Materials
  Digital Materials series consists of 3 1/2 floppy disks and 1 CD containing minutes, correspondence, reports, spreadsheets, budgets, proposals, graphics, photos, presentations, and other similar items from 1996 to 2004.
  - "Anne -- Arbor --Kids Sarah Anthony", 1 optical disks CD-R (Box 6)
  - Various working files 1996-2004, 1996-2004, 21 floppy disks 3.5" (Box 6)
    (include correspondence, reports, spreadsheets, budgets, proposals, graphics, photos, presentations, etc.)
- Audiovisual Materials
  Audiovisual Materials series contains 3 VHS tapes, 3 digital videocassettes, and 2 audiocassettes recording events, meetings, etc.
  - VHS Videotapes
    - Student Advocacy Center #1 undated, 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 6)
    - Student Advocacy Center #2 undated, 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 6)
    - A Celebration of the Life of Marcene root, Aug 24 2001, 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 6)
  - Digital Videocassettes
    - 12/10 Parts 1-3, 3 videotapes Mini-DV (Box 6)
  - Audiocassettes
    - Project Re-Enroll 1998, 1 audiocassettes (Box 6)
    - Board Meeting 9/14/2002, 1 audiocassettes (Box 6)